import { Question } from '../shared/question.model';

export const QUESTIONS: Question[] = [
    //{ question: 'In Star Wars Episode I - The Phantom Menace, Who Did Anakin Skywalker Belong To? (1 Word)', answer: 'Watto' },
    { question: 'In Star Wars Episode IV - A New Hope, for whom was Han Solo owed? (1 Word)', answer: 'Jabba' },
    //{ question: 'In the beggining of Episode III, what Sith do the Jedi face and defeat in General Grievous\'s ship? (2 Words)', answer: 'Count Dooku' },
   // { question: 'Who are the Guards of General Grievous? (1 Word)', answer: 'Magnaguards' },
    //{ question: 'In the Episode III, where is Obi-Wan going to investigate and search for General Grievous? (1 Word)', answer: 'Utapau' },
    { question: 'On what planet Leia is sent in the end of Episode III? (1 Word)', answer: 'Alderaan' },
    //{ question: 'On what planet Luke is sent in the end of Episode III? (1 Word)', answer: 'Tatooine' },
    { question: 'In Star Wars Episode V - Empire Strikes Back, at the beginning of the movie where the Rebel base is located? (1 Word)', answer: 'Hoth' },
    { question: 'In Star Wars Episode V - Empire Strikes Back, where does Luke Skywalker travel to be trained by Master Yoda? (1 Word)', answer: 'Dagobah' },
    //{ question: 'In Star Wars Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back, what is the most famous phrase spoken by Darth Vader? (5 Words)', answer: 'Luke, I am your father' },
    //{ question: 'What is the real name of Darth Vader? (2 Words)', answer: 'Anakin Skywalker' }
];